{
    "subject": "resource/Westfield_Middle_School",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Westfield Middle School is a school in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.The School is situated on Chester Road, and is the Queens Park area's only Middle School. The school usually takes pupils from Queens Park Lower school and Priory Lower School. Most of Westfield's graduating students go on to attend Biddenham Upper School.Westfield School is distinctive in that it has won International School status and is a Sports College.  Over 27 different languages are spoken at the school and many faiths are celebrated.Bedford Borough Council had decided to implement a two-tier education system in the borough, meaning that  all middle schools in the area will close. However since the failure to secure Building Schools for the future money, the notice to close Westfield Middle and other middle schools has been taken back.",
    "human_readable": "Westfield Middle School is a school located in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9433531165122986,
            "question": "Where is Westfield Middle School located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914143443107605,
            "question": "In which town is Westfield Middle School situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9054344892501831,
            "question": "Is Westfield Middle School in England or another country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8607591986656189,
            "question": "What is the name of the borough where Westfield Middle School is located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8299688696861267,
            "question": "What is the name of the park near Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120641708374023,
            "question": "What type of institution is Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7712804079055786,
            "question": "Are there any notable features about Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7254990935325623,
            "question": "Is Westfield Middle School a public or private school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.680217981338501,
            "question": "Can you provide the full address of Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4073559641838074,
            "question": "Does Westfield Middle School offer primary or secondary education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Westfield Middle School is a school located in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.",
            "html": "dbpedia_685_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide the full address of Westfield Middle School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_685_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Westfield Middle School a public or private school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_685_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable features about Westfield Middle School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_685_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_685_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple \"Westfield Middle School is a school located in Queens Park, Bedford, UK\" can be evaluated as follows:\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_685/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt states that:\n\"Westfield Middle School is a school in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.\"\n\nThis information supports the triple.\n\nTherefore, the output is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Westfield Middle School is a school located in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.\" Specifically, one of the documents states: \"Westfield Middle School is a school in Queens Park, Bedford, UK.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}